樂隊注意  向前齊步走
Band, forward march!
十秒倒數開始
Ten count to the VS,
二  一  開始
in two, one... go.
Behati到位了
I got Behati.
Doutzen在這
Doutzen is here.
Adriana還有20秒
Got 20 seconds for Adriana.
Ale在我這
I have Ale with me.
第五個是Alessandra
Five's following Alessandra.
給第七個來個特寫  鏡頭到第七個
Seven, close-up-- let me go to seven.
她轉身時給個特寫
Give me a close-up when she turns.
-漂亮  -Lindsay  倒數第三位  第十個
- Beautiful. - Lindsay, ten of 12.
-Lily到了  -這就來
- Lily's in the house. - There she goes.
Elsa開始走台
Elsa is walking.
Karlie在這  Karlie候場
Here comes Karlie. Stand by, Karlie.
-Candice出場  -這可是價值千萬的胸罩
- Go, Candice! - That's the $10 million bra.
讓她上場  讓她走  快點
Let her go, let her go, let her go!
我好緊張啊
I'm nervous!
後台誰負責首飾
Who's doing the jewelry back here?!
準備讓Taylor Swift從左側登台
Stand by to send Taylor Swift from stage left.
她來了
She's coming.
-開始  -第一位準備從六號門入場
- Here we go. - Stand by for the first girl on six.
上Fall Out Boy的佈景
Preset Fall Out Boy.
一切就緒  準備開始
We're a-rockin' and we're a-rollin'.
-開始緊張了  -你看上去美極了
- Getting nervous. - You look amazing!
-看著就身價百萬  -好極了
- Looks good for one million! - Awesome.
Bahati就在這  她來了  她來了
Bahati's right here. She's made it, she's made it.
A Great Big World準備就緒
A Great Big World in position.
燈光全開
Light shining through!
Neon Jungle準備好
Stand by, Neon Jungle.
三  二  一  開始
Three,, two one, go!
女士們先生們
Ladies and gentlemen,
掌聲有請Fall Out Boy
please welcome to the stage, Fall Out Boy!
? Fall Out Boy - "My Song Knows What You Did in the Dark" ?
? B-B-Be careful making wishes in the dark, dark ?
? Can't be sure when they've hit their mark ?
? And besides in the mean, meantime ?
? I'm just dreaming of tearing you apart ?
? I'm in the de-details with the devil ?
? The world can never get me on my level ?
? I just got to get you off the cage ?
? I'm a young lover's rage ?
? Gonna need a spark to ignite ?
? My songs know what you did in the dark ?
? So light'em up, up, up ?
? Light'em up, up, up ?
? Light'em up, up ?
? I'm on fire ?
? Light'em up, up, up ?
? Light'em up, up ?
? I'm on fire ?
? In the dark, dark ?
女士們先生們  有請Taylor Swift
Ladies and gentlemen, Taylor Swift.
? Writers keep writing what they write ?
? Somewhere another pretty vein just died ?
? I've got the scars from tomorrow and I wish ?
? You could see that you're the antidote ?
? To everything except for me ?
? A constellation of tears on your lashes ?
? Burn everything you love then burn the ashes ?
? In the end everything collides?
? My childhood spat back out the monster that you see ?
? My songs know what you did in the dark ?
? So light'em up, up, up, light'em up, up, up ?
? Light'em up, up, up ?
? I'm on fire ?
? Light 'em up, up, up ?
? Light 'em up, up, up, light 'em up, up ?
? I'm on fire ?
? In the dark, dark ?
晚上好  紐約
Oh, good evening, New York City,
歡迎來到維多利亞的秘密時尚秀
and welcome to the Victoria's Secret fashion Show.
我是Taylor
My name is Taylor.
他們是我的朋友  Patrick  Pete  Andy和Joe
These are my friends Patrick, Pete, Andy and Joe,
他們是Fall Out Boy  而她們...
and they are Fall Out Boy. And these...
是2013年維密天使
are the 2013 Victoria's Secret Angels.
? My songs know what you did in the dark ?
? So light'em up, up, up ?
? Light'em up, up, up ?
? Light'em up, up, I'm on fire ?
? In the dark, dark ?
? Light'em up, up, up ?
? Light'em up, up, I'm on fire ?
太棒了
Whoo! Amazing!
我們把你領出去化妝做頭髮
Let's move you out and let's do hair and makeup,
細節出去弄
touchups outside.
有人看見Kasia了嗎
Does anyone have eyes on Kasia?
Behati在我這
I got Behati.
我們需要Candice到標記處來
We need Candice on this cross.
我看見她了  沒問題
I got her, I got her. No problem.
很好  Doutzen到位  我們準備好了
Oh, good. Doutzen is here. We're ready for you.
天使們準備就緒
We're good on models.
準備登台
We are standing by.
我覺得我從小到大
I have been walking up and down
就一直在模仿超模走秀
fake runways my whole life, I think.
我第一次知道時尚秀時
The first time I was introduced to a fashion show,
我好像才四歲
I was, like, four years old.
我的夢想
My dream was to walk in
就是參加維密時尚內衣秀
the Victoria's Secret Fashion Show.
對於來自巴西小鎮的我來說
Coming from a small town in Brazil,
這太了不起了
it's huge.
我只想成為那些女孩中的一員
I just wanted to be one of those girls,
加入這個不可思議的大家庭
you know, and wanted to be part of this incredible family.
我18歲時
When I turned 18,
我就定下目標
I had set a goal of being
要參加維密時尚內衣秀
in the Victoria's Secret Fashion Show
卻不知道這意味著什麼
and had no comprehension of what was ahead.
我當時年紀小  缺乏安全感  很害怕
I was young and insecure and very scared.
我來維密的第一件事
The first thing I did
就是參加時尚內衣秀的模特選拔
with Victoria's Secret was the fashion show casting.
很多人問我們
A lot of people ask us,
你們選拔都看重什麼
"What do you look for when you're casting?"
對我們來說  最重要的是找到
For us, it's very, very important to have someone
熱情向上  積極開朗的人
who's enthusiastic and always positive and always happy--
我們要找一位美麗健康的女性
this gorgeous, healthy woman.
我從沒這麼緊張過
I had never been more nervous in my entire life.
把果凍和水泥混起來
If you could mix Jell-O and a cement block together...
-就是當時我腿的感覺  -慢點  慢點
- that is how my legs felt. - Slow down, slow down.
這是個成為巨星的真正機會
This is a real opportunity to become a big star.
我當時很年輕  對我來說簡直不可思議
I was so young-- it was just mind-blowing for me
我能夠參加走秀  能夠站上天橋
that I'd booked the show and that I was there.
我見到了Heidi  Laetitia  Stephanie
I saw Heidi, I saw Laetitia, I saw Stephanie.
還有Tyra Banks  Gisele  Adriana
Tyra Banks, Gisele, Adriana...
天吶天吶  真不敢相信我居然在這
"Oh, my God, oh, my God. I can't believe I'm here.
她們太美了
They're so beautiful."
我從未想過能走上維密秀天橋
I never imagined that I would be on that runway.
第一次參與維密內衣秀
My first time doing the VS Fashion Show,
改變了我的模特生涯
that changed my entire career.
維密能推動你的事業
It definitely puts you in the next level.
提高了我的全球知名度
That's what really got me out into the whole entire world.
大家都知道你是誰
Everybody knows who you are.
這是段無與倫比的旅程
It's such an incredible journey.
歲月如梭
The years go by so fast.
真希望時間能走得慢一點
I wish it could slow down.
我到現在都還沒緩過神來  但我做到了
I still don't know how it happened, but here I am.
我成為了維密天使
I made it.
我是位幸運的女孩
I'm just one lucky girl.
女士們先生們  掌聲歡迎A Great Big World
Ladies and gentleman, please welcome A Great Big World!
?A Great Big World - "Say Something"?
? Say something, I'm giving up on you ?
? I'll be the one, if you want me to ?
? Anywhere, I would've followed you ?
? Say something, I'm giving up on you ?
? And I... ?
? Am feeling so small ?
? It was over my head ?
? I know nothing at all ?
? And I... ?
? Will stumble and fall ?
? I'm still learning to love ?
? Just starting to crawl ?
? Say something, I'm giving up on you ?
? I'm sorry that I couldn't get to you ?
? Anywhere, I would've followed you ?
? Say something, I'm giving up on you ?
? And I... ?
? Will swallow my pride ?
? You're the one that I love ?
? And I'm saying good-bye ?
? Say something I'm giving up on you ?
? And I'm sorry that I couldn't get to you ?
? And anywhere, I would've followed you ?
? Say something I'm giving up on you ?
? Say something ?
收到  Nick快去吧
Copy that! Nick, go!
讓Lily走  你去幫忙
Release Lily and go help.
-讓天使們過  -"迷海遺艦"馬上開始
- Let the girls through. - Going into Shipwreck.
大伙  翅膀來咯  借過
Okay, guys, wings coming to you, wings coming to you.
我不知道被困在孤島上是什麼感覺
I don't know how it feels to be stuck on a deserted island.
-我一定會喜歡  -我會很討厭
- I would love it. - I would hate it.
我喜歡沙灘  也喜歡大海
I love the beach. I love the ocean.
要看誰與我同行
It depends who I could bring.
隨便吧  這就行了  對吧
Whatever. That-That'll do, right?
我會帶著...
I would bring...
手機
my phone.
衝浪板
A surfboard.
燒烤爐
A barbecue.
一把刀
A knife.
一位強壯的男士
A really strong man.
無線網絡
無線網絡不能少
And obviously we need Wi-Fi.
衛星電話
A satellite telephone.
-我的孩子和家人  -酒
- My kids and my family. - A drink.
需要生火嗎
Should we build a fire?
我能鑽木取火  我可是非洲人吶
I can make fire. I'm from Africa.
算了  一點結果都沒有
All right, we got nothing.
一定會很有樂趣的
We'll make it fun.
帶我離開這座島
Oh, get me off this island!
誰都不會來救我們
I don't think anybody's coming.
情況可能會更糟
It could be worse.
我們至少還有彼此
At least we have each other.
麻煩給Taylor Swift換裝
Taylor Swift into next outfit, please.
天吶
Oh, my God!
好  準備下一環節  快準備
All right, prep next section! Prep next section!
他們去樓下找Cara了
Cara, they're looking for downstairs --
還在弄她的服裝
they're fixing her little outfit,
還有Jourdan沒找著人
and Jourdan -- those are the only ones I haven't seen.
廣告過後  "巴黎之夜"即將登場
After the break, spend a night with us in Paris.
精彩盡在CBS
Only CBS.
天吶
Oh, my God!
我們以試衣模特為標準
The looks model is the model that we use
制訂走秀服裝
to try on the fashion show outfits.
許多試衣模特都成為了維密巨星
Looks models become big Victoria's Secret stars.
包括Ale  Lindsay和Candice
We've had Ale, Lindsay and Candice.
我可以試穿所有服裝
I got to try every single outfit.
試戴首飾和羽毛
Trying on jewelry and feathers.
服裝的靈感令人驚喜
I was blown away by the ideas.
你們居然還有新點子
I can't believe you guys still have ideas left.
感覺不錯  我喜歡
This feels good. I like it.
試衣模特不好當
Being a looks model is actually a very difficult job,
你就像個衣架子
because you're a human mannequin,
穿著半成品
and you're being picked and poked,
任憑設計師在你身上來回裁剪
and they're literally making the outfit on you.
嗨  Barbara
Hey, Barbara.
Barbara Fialho是我們近幾年的試衣模特
Barbara Fialho, who's been the looks model for the past couple of years.
她對一切充滿了熱情
She is so enthusiastic about everything.
她鼓舞了我們
She inspires us,
讓整個團隊都非常愉快
and she really gets the whole team in a great mood.
團隊堹鄏處arbara這樣的人
It's so important for us to have
是非常重要的
someone like Barbara on the team.
這份工作棒極了
It's such an amazing job to have.
這是我呀
That's me. Oh, yeah.
去年是我的首秀  非常棒
The first show last year was amazing.
在那之後  我的生活改變了許多
Since the last show, so much has changed.
我拿到了第一份化妝廣告
I did my first major cosmetic campaign.
參與了紀梵希的許多拍攝
I've done a lot of work for Givenchy.
我的模特生涯更上了一層樓
Everything has come to a different level.
-我們為你選了一套服裝  -真的嗎
- We chose an outfit for you. - You did?
你一定會喜歡
We think you're going to like it.
天吶
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
我一開始就看上了這個
This is my favorite one, from the beginning.
這是你應得的
You deserve it, you deserve it.
旅途繼續
The journey continues.
再見
Bye.
Adriana準備  第五首音樂
Stand by, Adriana. Music, track five!
投影和燈柱準備好
Projections Y-55, lamp posts in at two!
Adriana在穿翅膀
Adriana's getting her wings on.
她從舞台左側進場
She'll be stage left.
Adriana  還有20秒進場
20 seconds, Adriana.
? Miley Cyrus - "FU" ?
? Oh, you broke my heart ?
? I told you ?
? I was weak for love ?
? But then you went around ?
? And did what you wanted to do ?
? And now I'm crying ?
? Crying ?
? Ooh, seemed like everything was going fine ?
? I found love that I thought was gonna last ?
? Then I accidentally saw a few things in your cell ?
? I even lol'ed ?
? Man, I should've known ?
? Why, why you're doing what you do ?
? You, you might as well just tell the honest truth ?
? See, I'm not really down with this ?
? This ain't no Texan ?
? No, I got no biz, but it is what it is ?
? I don't really have much to say ?
? I was over it ?
? The second that I saw her name ?
? I got two, two ?
? Two letters for you ?
? One of them's F! And the other one's U ?
? 'Cause what you gotta do is go get yourself a clue ?
? Only two, two, two ?
? Letters to choose ?
? One of them's F! And the other one's U ?
? SMH I'm pressing send on you ?
? Could've been this, could've been that ?
? We done been there, we done been back ?
? You ain't with it, could've said that ?
? Why you trippin', let me hear that ?
? I ain't trying to argue all morning ?
? I do it all for you ?
? You know you're my rider ?
? Baby, let me show you ?
? Oh, I know what's been going on ?
? Don't even try to act like Mr. Super Nonchalant ?
? What makes you think I'd stick around ?
? I'm not as stupid as you sound, and you ?
? Sound really dumb right now ?
? From A to Zed ?
? I got a lot of nasty things ?
? Blowing up in my head ?
? But none of them are worth my time ?
? You're not even worth this rhyme ?
? And I don't, I don't ?
? Give a flying ?
? I don't really have much to say ?
? I was over it the second that I ?
? Saw her name ?
? I got two ?
?Two, two letters for you ?
? One of them's F ?
? And the other one's U ?
? 'Cause what you gotta do is go get yourself a clue ?
? Only two, two, two ?
? Letters to choose ?
? One of them's F! And the other one's U ?
? SMH ?
? I'm pressing send on you ?
? Ooh, ooh, two letters for you ?
? Yeah(letters for you) ?
? What you trippin' on, huh?
? Girl, you know you're wrong, huh ?
? Don't let these girls drive you crazy ?
? I don't really have much to say ?
? I was over it the second that I saw her name ?
? I got two, two, two letters for you ?
? One of them's F! And the other one's U ?
? 'Cause what you gotta do is go get yourself a clue ?
? Only two, two, two, letters to choose ?
? One of them's F ?
?And the other one's U ?
? SMH, I'm pressing send on you ?
? I got two, two, two letters for you ?
停放乾冰  乾冰停下
Let's stop atmosphere now, please. Stop atmosphere now.
Clyde  倒數60秒  撤下巴黎街燈
Clyde, cue 60-- the Parisian lamp post out.
? 'Cause what you gotta do ?
? Is go get yourself a clue ?
? Only two, two, two, two ?
? I'm pressing send on you ?
今年的假日廣告是在巴黎拍的
This year, we shot the holiday commercial in Paris.
開拍
And action!
猶如夢境一般
It felt like a dream.
妙不可言
It was awesome.
我們決定在夜間拍攝
We decided to shoot at night.
午夜拍廣告  感覺有些淘氣
It feels a little naughty to shoot at midnight.
從全新的視角來拍攝
It's such a different way
內衣和天使們
to see the lingerie and see us.
我們睡了一白天  晚上八點才開始做造型
We slept all day, we'd go to hair and makeup at 8:00,
接著拍了一夜廣告
and then shoot all through the night.
我們的生物鐘的確與眾不同
Our sleeping patterns were very interesting.
凌晨六點  我們還在香榭麗捨大街拍外景
At 6 a.m., we're shooting right in front of the Champs-Elysees.
當時我只穿著內衣
I'm just walking around in my wings
戴著翅膀走來走去  沒啥大不了的
in my bra and underwear, no big deal.
開拍
And action!
巴黎的夜晚燈火絢爛
Paris is luminous.
它是光明之城
It's the City of Lights,
我們真的點亮了它的光芒
and we lit it up, literally.
維密公司花下重金
Victoria's Secret paid
讓埃菲爾鐵塔整晚閃爍
to keep the Eiffel Tower lit all night.
難以置信的美麗特別  浪漫至極
It was unbelievably beautiful and special and romantic.
我當時真是凍得要命
It was freezing cold.
天上還下著雪
It was practically snowing.
要是讓我受凍
Put me in a cold situation,
我就會不開心
and I'm not the happy girl.
這次的拍攝場面特別宏大
It's such a massive production.
拍了許多動人心魄的美麗場景
Beautiful, epic scenes.
是展現演技的好機會
It's an opportunity to perform.
為了展現性感  我通常會做這樣的表情
To turn on sexy, I usually will do one of these.
這是搞怪版Behati
This is goofy Behati, um,
有點二的Behati
being her stupid self.
這是性感版Candice
Ths is sexy Candice.
這才叫性感
And this is sexy.
有何貴幹
What?
大概有一千多位娛記
There was, like, a thousand paparazzi
想拍到我們的照片
trying to get pictures of us...
但廣告拍攝依舊順利
But we got the shot.
沒什麼能阻擋維密假日廣告
Nothing can stop a VS holiday commercial.
Lais非常出色
Lais is simply amazing.
她是我所認識最甜美
She's the sweetest,
最溫柔  最美麗的姑娘
most gentle, beautiful thing I've ever seen.
我從沒在天橋上摔倒過
I've never fallen on the runway.
但世事無常  一旦發生後果極其沉重
But it's, you know, it happens, and it's awful when it does.
參加維密秀是每個女孩的夢想
To be in this show is a dream for every girl.
我十分重視它
It's a big deal.
去年我參加了綵排
Last year, I got there to do the rehearsal.
但不知道怎麼回事
Then, I don't know how it happened.
我突然摔倒了
I just fell down.
我覺得我的腳踝斷了
I thought I broke my ankle.
恐懼感會一直縈繞在你腦海中
It's always in the back of your mind.
這件事真的特別可怕
It's a scary thing.
在綵排中扭傷腳踝
At the rehearsal,
然後無法參加走秀
hurt your foot, and you can't do the show?
這事太讓人傷心了
It was a very sad moment.
好了
Okay.
大家都嚇壞了
Everybody was freaking out
因為他們說
because they said it looked like
看上去很嚴重
her foot literally broke,
她的腳踝好像真的斷了
snapped from underneath her.
我當然特別沮喪
Of course, I was very upset.
我開始哭
You know, I start to cry.
當時的場面很沉重
It was pretty heavy.
第二天  我醒來
And the next day, I woke up,
試著站起來
and then, I tried to put my feet on the ground.
還是不行
No.
沒法走路
No way to walk.
我不得不穿起她的裝扮  替她走秀
I had to go out there and walk the show in her look.
那感覺太糟糕了
It felt really horrible.
穿著她的裝扮太難受了
I felt so bad putting that outfit on,
因為那本是她的  不該由我去展現
'cause it wasn't mine, I wasn't supposed to have it.
今年  我做了更充足的準備
This year, I'm more than prepared for this show.
Lais  出來讓我們看看吧
Okay, Lais, can we see your outfit?
辣妹喲
Wow! It is hot!
試衣的時候
In the fitting,
我告訴他們  如果我又摔倒
I told them, if I fall again,
我一定會撲扇著翅膀飛起來
of course I'm gonna use my wings to fly.
因為去年你出了意外  所以今年
Because of what happened to you last year, we wanted you to know
我們希望你來走這個單元的開場
that we're going to have you open the section of the show
叫作"天堂飛鳥"
which is called "Birds of Paradise."
感謝你
Thank you. Thank you.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
今晚我無比興奮快樂
Tonight, I'm more than excited, happy.
也很緊張
Nervous.
我希望Lais今年
I want for Lais, this year,
能走一場最美妙的秀
to have the most incredible show,
穿最熱辣的衣服
to have the most incredible outfit,
希望一切都如她所願
to have whatever she wants.
我們都會在她身後支持她
We're all gonna be behind her this year, and be, like,
為她歡呼
"Yeah!"
我一定會去後台祝賀她
I will definitely find Lais backstage.
希望她享受最美時刻
I want her to just have the best time.
上吧
Kill it.
Fall Out Boy登台吧
Preset Fall Out Boy, go!
? Fall Out Boy – "The Phoenix" ?
? Put on your war paint ?
? You are a brick tied to me that's dragging me down ?
? Strike a match and I'll burn you to the ground ?
姑娘  上吧
Go, baby, go!
? We are the jack-o-lanterns in July ?
? Setting fire to the sky ?
? Here it comes this rising tide, so come on ?
? Put on your war paint ?
? Cross walks and crossed hearts and hope-to-dies ?
? Silver clouds with grey linings ?
? So we can take the world back from a heart attack ?
? One maniac at a time we will take it back ?
? Time crawls on ?
? When you're waiting for the song to start ?
? Dance alone to the beat of your heart ?
? Hey, young blood, doesn't it feel ?
? Like our time is running out ?
? I'm gonna change you like a remix ?
? Then I'll raise you like a phoenix ?
? It's our vintage misery ?
? No, I think it looked a little better on me ?
? I'm gonna change you like a remix ?
? Then I'll raise you like a phoenix ?
? Bring home the boys and scrap, scrap metal the tanks ?
? Get hitched, make a career out of robbing banks ?
? Because the world is just a teller ?
? And we are wearing black masks ?
? "You broke our spirit" Says the note we pass ?
? Take the world back from a heart attack ?
? One maniac at a time, we'll take it back ?
? Time crawls on ?
? When you're waiting for the song to start ?
? Dance alone to the beat of your heart ?
? Hey, young blood, doesn't it feel ?
? Like our time is running out ?
? I'm gonna change you like a remix ?
? Then I'll raise you like a phoenix ?
? It's our vintage misery ?
? No, I think it looked a little better on me ?
? I'm gonna change you like a remix ?
? Then I'll raise you like a phoenix ?
? The war is won before it's begun ?
維密秀  歡呼聲在哪
Victoria Secret, make some noise!
?Release the doves, surrender love ?
?The war is won before it's begun ?
?The war is won(wave the white flag) ?
?Before it's begun(wave the white flag) ?
?Release the dove(wave the white flag) ?
?Surrender love(wave the white flag) ?
?The war is won before it's begun(wave the white flag) ?
?Release the doves(wave the white flag) ?
?Surrender love(wave the white flag) ?
?Hey, young blood ?
?Doesn't it feel like our time is running out ?
?I'm gonna change you like a remix ?
?Then I'll raise you like a phoenix ?
注意翅膀  小心點兒
Okay, watch the wings. Watch the wings.
這是我正常的樣子
This is my natural look.
這是我性感的樣子
And this... is my sexy look.
等等  我都不知道我性感是什麼樣
Oh, wait-- I don't know what my sexy look is!
矮油  這樣性感嗎  你確定嗎
Oh, gosh, do I look sexy? Are you sure about that?
關鍵在頭髮
It's all about the hair.
走秀風來一個
Now on to the runway.
好樣的
There we go.
真的好好笑
It's just too funny.
這才是我性感的樣子
This is my sexy look.
下節精彩
Still to come...
Taylor Swift和Neon Jungle登場
Taylor Swift and Neon Jungle.
雙重驚喜哦
That's double trouble.
精彩盡在CBS
Only CBS.
?Let's go ?
?I wanna go around the world ?
?And party with the girls ?
?Let's go ?
?And when I get there, when I get there ?
?When I'm there I wanna go ?
?I wanna go crazy ?
?I wanna go ?
?That's where I wanna go ?
?I wanna go cra-cra-crazy-zy-zy ?
?We like to sleep all day... ?
維密時尚內衣秀
加入維密話題
#vsfashionshow.
?This is how we like to live our life ?
?Hands up ?
今晚這場秀堛漫狾頃玼S
All of the models that are in the show tonight
其實都是社交媒體上的明星
are literally the rock stars of social media.
發些東西到網上很好啊
It's a great way to get stuff out there.
?Let's go ?
我最開始接觸的是Twitter
I started with Twitter.
我從那堭o到所有的消息
That's where I get all of my news.
沒有Instagram沒法活啊
I would die without Instagram.
我覺得Facebook很棒
Facebook, I think, is great.
誰是爆照狂人
Who's the most fearless poster?
Cara
Cara.
不好意思
Sorry.
她在社交媒體上很有影響力
She's remarkably powerful in social media.
這很好啊
That's a good point, though, yeah.
網絡平台很自由
There's so much freedom.
沒有任何限制  暢所欲言
There is no boundaries; you can say whatever you want.
她特別大膽
She is fearless.
我沒考慮太多  想做什麼就做
I don't think about it, I just do it.
我喜歡她這態度
I like her attitude about that.
她們的粉絲多得嚇人
It's crazy how many followers they have.
我在Instagram上有290萬粉絲
2.9 million people follow me on Instagram.
總共得有上千萬的粉絲
Collectively, it's in the tens of millions.
我每隔三四分鐘
I pick up my phone
就會拿起手機看看
at least every three to four minutes.
每次打開手機  都會看到新的東西
Every time you pick it up, there's something else to look at.
我發的大多數東西
I like to post a balance
都關於家庭  工作和慈善
between family, work, and charity.
鼓舞人心的名人名言
Inspiring quotes.
積極向上的消息
Positive messages.
有時我發了不該發的照片
Sometimes I post photos I shouldn't.
我所擁有的一切
In one second, I could
可能瞬間毀於一旦
screw up everything I have.
就好像按了一個巨大的紅色按鈕
It's like the big red button.
一切瞬間爆炸
And everything explodes.
小心哦
Be careful.
悔推  你不能發任何讓你後悔的東西
Tweegret-- You shouldn't tweegret anything.
我想我刪過一些東西
I feel like I've deleted something before,
但我不記得是什麼了
but I can't remember what it is.
-刪除  -我還沒碰到情況糟糕到
- Delete. - I haven't had, like, a shocking moment
我得找我的經紀人  讓他"快刪掉"
that I had to get... my agency is like, "Get that off!"
Instagram蒙羞
Instashame.
生命苦短  沒空在Instagram上蒙羞
Life is too short for Instashame.
隨便去谷歌搜一搜
You can just go on Google
很容易就搜到我的屁股了
and see my butt anyway.
太瘋狂了
That's crazy.
咱們現在應該幹點壞事兒
We should do something bad right now.
-我知道  有"助"形象  -沒錯
- I know, it'd be great for our image. - Yeah.
這個品牌在世界上如此聞名
One of the reasons the brand is so
也得益於她們那些社交網絡活動
well-known worldwide is because of their social activity.
這也是工作的一部分
It's part of the job.
是嗎
Is it?
維密時尚內衣秀
VSfashionshow.
準備  所有粉紅女郎
Okay, stand by, all Pink girls.
請所有粉紅模特到前台
Please, can I have all Pink models onstage now?
這是我第一次走台
It's my first time walking,
穿上這身美麗的衣服還有翅膀
and I got this amazing outfit with wings.
真是無比榮幸
I mean, it's such an honor.
其他人為我第一次表演而緊張
Makes me nervous that other people are nervous for me
這也讓我很緊張
for being here for the first time.
我臉上這傻乎乎的笑停不下來
I can't take my-- this, like, stupid smile that's on my face--
我都笑了好幾周了
it's been there for, like, weeks.
Neon Jungle請到開場位置  馬上
Neon Jungle to opening positions, please-- now.
女士們先生們  掌聲歡迎
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome to America
無與倫比的Neon Jungle
the incredible Neon Jungle.
? Neon Jungle - "Trouble" ?
? Trouble ?
? I don't look for trouble, but trouble looks for me ?
? And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
? They say, "Here comes a hurricane" ?
? "Trouble is her middle name" ?
? But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me ?
? I don't look for trouble ?
? But trouble looks for me ?
? And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
? They say, "Here comes a hurricane" ?
? "Trouble is her middle name" ?
? But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me ?
? I just want to live a quiet life ?
? I'll make an excellent wife ?
? Man, I swear I really try ?
? But some boys they just can't eat it whole ?
? Trouble is my name, you know ?
? I don't look for trouble, but trouble looks for me ?
? And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
? They say, "Here comes a hurricane" ?
? "Trouble is her middle name" ?
? But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me ?
? I don't look for trouble, but trouble looks for me ?
? And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
? They say that girl got so many sides ?
? Uh, I'm a Gemini ?
? But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me ?
? Lights up, let's have a toke ?
? Pour more whiskey in my Coke ?
? Never been one of the herd ?
? Flippin' everyone the bird ?
? People say that I am heartless ?
? I've just learned to use my heart less ?
? I go hard 'cause I'm the hardest ?
? And we ain't even started yet ?
? Trouble ?
? I don't look for trouble, but trouble looks for me ?
? And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
? They say, "Here comes a hurricane" ?
? "Trouble is her middle name" ?
? But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me ?
? Hey, hey, I don't look for trouble ?
? But trouble looks for me ?
? And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
? They say, "Here comes a hurricane" ?
? "Trouble is her middle name" ?
? But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me ?
? Trouble ?
謝謝  謝謝大家
Thank you. Thank you.
Taylor來表演啦
Taylor's in the show.
好激動
Excitement.
她才華橫溢
She's amazingly talented
還那麼漂亮
and so gorgeous.
Taylor是典型的美國女孩
Taylor is this all-American girl,
她就像美國夢
she's like the American Dream,
我們一定會玩得很開心
and I think we're gonna have a lot of fun.
太棒了
Okay, awesome.
-我們已經是好多年的朋友  -閨蜜
- We've been friends for years. - Besties.
她在表演時  我也在表演
And getting to see her do her job at the same time as I'm doing my job...
-我知道  -太瘋狂了
- I know. - ...it's crazy.
麻煩妞來了...
- Trouble.  - Trouble.
廣告之後  我的閨蜜Taylor Swift即將登台
After the break, my girl Taylor Swift.
要如何成為一位天使呢
What does it take to be an Angel?
付出一切
Everything you've got.
即使那樣也還不夠
An end even than's out enough.
這需要集中精力
It takes focus,
需要決心  需要耐力
it takes commitment, and it takes endurance.
但缺乏力量的美是空洞的
But beauty is nothing without strength.
這些姑娘的訓練堪比專業運動員
These girls train like professionahll athletes
她們為了理想身材而努力鍛煉
and they really work for the bodies that they want.
Michael把我當拳手一樣訓練
Michael trains me like a fighter.
而且這場搏擊永不停止
And the fight never actually ends.
我為走秀而鍛煉
I work out for the runway,
但更多是為人生而鍛煉
but mostly I work out for life.
Adriana有真本事
Adriana is the real deal.
她體能心理都很強大
It's as mental as it is physical for her.
她的勁頭勢不可擋
And she's unstoppable.
我喜歡大汗淋漓
I like to sweat.
我喜歡運動不止
I like to keep moving.
當我愛上某種東西  我會全情投入
When I love something, I commit.
你跟Adriana一起走
You're walking with Adriana.
候場了  Adriana
Stand by, Adriana.
Taylor來了  候場
Taylor's entrance. Stand by.
Behati到位
Behati's right here.
她到了  她到了
She's made it, she's made it.
Taylor就位
We have Taylor!
請她上台  有請Taylor Swift
Send her. Send Taylor Swift.
女士們先生們  請熱烈歡迎
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome back
獨一無二的Taylor Swift
the one and only Taylor Swift.
? Taylor Swift - "I Knew Your Were Trouble" ?
? Once upon a time, a few mistakes ago ?
? I was in your sights, you got me alone ?
? You found me, you found me ?
? You found me-ee-ee-ee-ee ?
? I guess you didn't care ?
? And I guess I liked that ?
? And when I fell hard, you took a step back ?
? Without me, without me ?
? Without me-ee-ee-ee-ee-ee ?
? And he's long gone ?
? When he's next to me ?
? And I realize ?
? The blame is on me ?
? 'Cause I knew you were trouble when you walked in ?
? So shame on me now ?
? Flew me to places I never been ?
? Till you put me down, oh ?
? I knew you were trouble when you walked in ?
? Shame on me now ?
? Flew me to places I never been ?
? Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground ?
? Trouble, trouble, trouble ?
? No apologies ?
? He'll never see you cry ?
? Pretends he doesn't know that he's the reason why ?
? You're drowning, you're drowning ?
? You're drown-ee-ee-ee-ee-ing ?
? Now, I heard you moved on from whispers on the street ?
? A new notch in your belt is all I'll ever be ?
? Now I see ?
? Now I see, now I see ee-ee-ee-ee?
? He was long gone ?
? When he met me ?
? And I realize ?
? The joke is on me ?
? Yeah ?
? I knew you were trouble when you walked in ?
? So shame on me now ?
? Flew me to places I never been ?
? Till you put me down, oh ?
? I knew you were trouble when you walked in ?
? So shame on me now ?
? Flew me to places I never been ?
? Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground ?
? Trouble, trouble, trouble ?
? Trouble, trouble, trouble, ?
? And the saddest fear ?
? Comes creeping in?
? That you never loved me ?
? Or her or anyone ?
? Or anything ?
? Yeah... ?
? So shame on me now ?
? Flew me to places I never been ?
? Never been till you put me down, oh ?
? Knew you were trouble when you walked in ?
? So shame on me now ?
? Flew me to places I never been ?
? Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground ?
? Trouble, trouble, trouble ?
? I knew you were trouble when you walked in ?
? Knew you were trouble when you walked in ?
? Trouble, trouble, trouble. ?
進第七首音樂  二  一  走
Now music track seven in two, one-- go!
上吧  寶貝兒們  上上上
Go, babes. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
來來來
Come on, come on.
太讚了  贊贊贊
Well done, well done.
? Lady Gaga - "Applause" ?
? The applause, applause, applause ?
? Give me that thing that I love ?
? I'll turn the lights on ?
? Put your hands up, make 'em touch, touch ?
? Give me that thing that I love ?
? I'll turn the lights on ?
? Put your hands up, make'em touch ?
? Make it real loud... ?
? A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E. Make it real loud ?
? Put your hands up, make'em touch ?
? Make it real loud... ?
? A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E. Make it real loud ?
? Put your hands up, make'em touch, touch ?
? A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E ?
? Make it real loud ?
? Put your hands up, make'em touch, touch ?
? A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E. Make it real loud ?
? I live for the applause ?
? Applause, applause ?
? I live for the applause-plause ?
? Live for the applause-plause... ?
2013年走秀圓滿落幕
Okay, class of 2013.
現在要在後台拍個照
So, we're shooting something backstage about now.
大家要拍個合影
They're fielding a photograph.
任務很艱巨  你們要拍個集體大合影
Now the hard part. You have to have a photo all together.
2013年大合影
The 2013 shot.
你們要和Taylor照吧
You want Taylor.
對哦  誰能抗拒Taylor Swift呢
Yes. Who can say no to Taylor Swift?
大家靠近一點
Now, get in close together.
一  二  三
One, two, three!
謝謝
Thank you.
太棒了  謝謝  收工咯
Fantastic. Thank you. Thats 'a wrap.
■
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
維多利亞的秘密
時尚內衣秀
翻譯：美腿熊貓    妞
兒圓滾滾     阿曦
西之      小而
堅挺飯      夕橙
校對：小細腿子衿羨慕大長腿
澤川
傅莉迪
饅頭年年見
時間軸：一不小心做維秘的ans
處心積慮做維秘的萌
特效：蠟筆小新的眉毛
後期：孤帆
總監：寫作總監讀
作打雜的澤川
迷海遺艦
嗨  老媽
快報警
巴黎之夜
天堂飛鳥
粉紅女郎征服世界
悔推
Instagram蒙羞
維密時尚秀
粉紅羅網
私人教練
白雪天使
攝影師